voscast.com 2019-04-20

# VosCast - SHOUTcast Hosting

**VosCast Terms of Service**  
By registering, purchasing hosting, or using the site, you are agreeing to the following Terms of Service. 

**1\. Your Account**

 **a.** We reserve the full right to terminate your account at any time, with or without given notice. Your account WILL be terminated if you are found in violation of any of these terms. 

**b.** If your account is terminated due to a violation of the Terms of Service, a refund will not be provided. If your account is terminated for some other reason, it is at our sole discretion if a refund will be given. 

**c.** In order to register on our site, you are required to have a valid unique email address. 

**d.** When ordering a SHOUTcast server from VosCast, you are only renting the SHOUTcast server. All services remain the property of VosCast. 

**2\. Usage**

 **a.** You may only use up to the maximum bitrate that your purchased with your server when broadcasting. If you attempt to use a higher bitrate, you will automatically be disconnected from our server. 

**b.** Servers may only be used for the services they were intended and you may not install or use unauthorized third party programs. Unauthorized usage, such as attempting to access or interfere with other clients data, will result in suspension of your services. 

**c.** Your usage must not interfere with the services we provide to other customers. 

**3\. Licensing and Other Legal Obligations**

 **a.** You are responsible for meeting the legal requirements for your station. This may include, but is not limited to, internet radio licensing. 

**b.** We claim no responsibility whatsoever for what you choose to stream on your server. 

**c.** You may not use our services to distribute adult or illegal material. 

**4\. Liability**

 **a.** VosCast.com will not be liable for delays or failure in performance caused by acts of God, war, terrorism, strike, labor dispute, work stoppage, fire, act of government, or any other cause, whether similar or dissimilar, beyond our control. 

**b.** VosCast.com reserves the right to restrict, alter, or modify fees, benefits, rules, regulations, special offers, membership terms and conditions or terminate services at any time and without notice. 

**c.** VosCast.com is not liable to store any statistical data regarding servers, such as listener information. 

**5\. Service Availability**

 **a.** We make reasonable efforts to ensure services are available 24 hours a day, 7 days a week for as long as you have paid for them. Sometimes, however, for a number of reasons, services may be unavailable to you. You recognize and acknowledge that on occasion, an event will occur causing services will be unavailable. We make no representation or warranty that our services will be uninterrupted. 

**6\. Unlimited Services**

 **a.** In the best interest of our subscribers, VosCast does not put an limit on the amount of listeners that may connect to the server, nor the amount of bandwidth a server may use. 

**b.** With SHOUTcast servers, the software requires a maximum number of listeners to be set. By default, your SHOUTcast server will be installed with a limit of 1,000 listeners. If needed, this may be increased at any time by contacting VosCast customer support. 

**c.** The unlimited service offered on our site is intended for personal sites, home businesses, and small businesses. Our service is not intended for large enterprises, or other stations better suited to a dedicated server. 

**7\. Auto DJ Service**

 **a.** "Auto DJ" is included as a free service with your VosCast account, that enables you to stream music from our servers to your SHOUTcast server. When renting a SHOUTcast server from VosCast, you are not paying for the Auto DJ service. For this reason, we offer no guarantees regarding the quality of this service. 

**b.** In order to use our free "Auto DJ" service, you will be required to agree to a separate terms of service for that service. These separate terms can be found at http://voscast.com/terms-auto-dj/

 **c.** We reserve the right to discontinue our free "Auto DJ" service at any time. 

**8\. Refunds**

 **a.** Refunds will only be issued at our sole discretion. Problems can typically be resolved by contacting customer support. 

**b.** Any chargebacks or reversed transactions made on your payments will result in your account being immediately terminated. 

**9\. Our Site**

 **a.** We cannot assure that the site is completely free from exploits. If a user is caught exploiting any area of VosCast.com, their account will be permanently terminated. 

**b.** We reserve the right to modify any of the information on the site at any given time. 

**10\. Other**

 **a.** You may review our privacy policy at the following link: <http://voscast.com/terms/#privacy>

**These terms of service were last modified on April 12, 2013.**

**VosCast Privacy Policy**  
We may be contacted at the following link: http://voscast.com/support/

 **1\. Personal Information**

**a.** Any personal information you provide for use on VosCast.com will not be given to any outside parties for any purpose. Information you provide is for use strictly on VosCast.com. 

**2\. How do we protect your information?**

 **a.** We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. Some user data is stored in your browser cookies. However, never, under any circumstances, is any sensitive data stored in your browser cookies. All user inputed data is stored in our databases (username, password, IP address, etc). Any sensitive information (such as passwords) is encrypted. Private information, such as credit card numbers, are never stored in our databases, and never will be. 

**3\. Third party sites**

 **a.** We may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these separate sites. 

**b.** We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties any of your personally identifiable information. However, we may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

**4\. Online Privacy Policy Only**

 **a.** This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**This policy was last modified on December 27, 2009.**
